<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FITNESS TIPS</string>
    <string name="squat">SQUAT</string>
    <string name="squat_desc">A squat is a strength exercise in which the trainee lowers their hips from a standing position and then stands back up. During the descent, the hip and knee joints flex while the ankle joint dorsiflexes; conversely the hip and knee joints extend and the ankle joint plantarflexes when standing up.</string>
    <string name="lunge">LUNGE</string>
    <string name="lunge_desc">A lunge can refer to any position of the human body where one leg is positioned forward with knee bent and foot flat on the ground while the other leg is positioned behind. It is used by athletes in cross-training for sports, by weight-trainers as a fitness exercise, and by practitioners of yoga as part of an asana regimen.</string>
    <string name="incline_dumbbell_press">INCLINE DUMBBELL</string>
    <string name="incline_dumbbell_press_desc">The incline dumbbell press is a free weight exercise designed to target the chest, shoulders, and triceps, independently hitting each side of the body. Unlike the more traditional flat bench press, the incline press shifts the movements focus to the upper portion of the pectoral muscle groups and the front of the shoulder. This allows for more significant hypertrophy (muscle growth) of the upper chest when the exercise is performed regularly.</string>
    <string name="bench_press">BENCH PRESS</string>
    <string name="bench_press_desc">The bench press, or chest press, is a weight training exercise where a person presses a weight upwards while lying horizontally on a weight training bench. Although the bench press is a full-body exercise, the muscles primarily used are the pectoralis major, the anterior deltoids, and the triceps, among other stabilizing muscles. A barbell is generally used to hold the weight, but a pair of dumbbells can also be used.</string>
    <string name="dip">DIP</string>
    <string name="dip_desc">A dip is an upper-body strength exercise. Close grip dips primarily train the triceps, with major synergists being the anterior deltoid, the pectoralis muscles, and the rhomboid muscles of the back. Wide shoulder width dips place additional emphasis on the pectoral muscles, similar in respect to the way a wide grip bench press would focus more on the pectorals and less on the triceps.</string>
    <string name="biceps_curl">BICEPS CURL</string>
    <string name="biceps_curl_desc">The bicep curl mainly targets the biceps brachii, brachialis and brachioradialis muscles. The biceps is stronger at elbow flexion when the forearm is supinated (palms turned upward) and weaker when the forearm is pronated. The brachioradialis is at its most effective when the palms are facing inward, and the brachialis is unaffected by forearm rotation. Therefore, the degree of forearm rotation affects the degree of muscle recruitment between the three muscles.</string>
    <string name="dead_lift">DEAD LIFT</string>
    <string name="dead_lift_desc">The deadlift is a weight training exercise in which a loaded barbell or bar is lifted off the ground to the level of the hips, torso perpendicular to the floor, before being placed back on the ground. It is one of the three powerlifting exercises, along with the squat and bench press, as well as a frequent lift in strongman. Two styles of deadlift are commonly used in competition settings: the conventional deadlift and the sumo deadlift. While both of these styles are permitted under the rules of powerlifting, only the conventional stance is permitted in strongman.</string>
    <string name="face_pull">FACE PULL</string>
    <string name="face_pull_desc">The face pull is a weight training exercise that primarily targets the musculature of the upper back and shoulders, namely the posterior deltoids, trapezius, rhomboids, as well as the infraspinatus and teres minor muscles of the rotator cuff. The face pull is considered an important exercise for shoulder health and stability</string>
    <string name="dumbbell_press">DUMBBELL PRESS</string>
    <string name="dumbbell_press_desc">Narrow grip (close grip): A bench press performed with the hands close together. It relies on the triceps to complete the pressing motion. Called the close grip bench press, this variation is best performed with arms in a near-vertical position to reduce strain placed upon the wrists, elbows, and shoulders. A close grip bench press can also be performed with dumbbells or a barbell with neutral grips.</string>
    <string name="triceps_extension">TRICEPS EXTENSION</string>
    <string name="triceps_extension_desc">A push-down is a strength training exercise used for strengthening the triceps muscles in the back of the arm. This exercise can also be called a tricep push-down or a two armed standing tricep extension. The exercise is completed by pushing an object downward against resistance. This exercise is an example of the primary function of the triceps, extension of the elbow joint.</string>
    <string name="shrug">SHRUG</string>
    <string name="shrug_desc">The shoulder shrug (usually called simply the shrug) is an exercise in weight training used to develop the upper trapezius muscle.The lifter stands erect, hands about shoulder width apart, and slowly raises the shoulders as high as possible, and then slowly lowers them, while not bending the elbows, or moving the body at all. </string>
    <string name="learn_more_icon_desc">Learn more</string>
</resources>